

Omokefe Ovie

Frontend developer

About Me

Dedicated and detail-oriented self taught Frontend web developer with 1 year 6 month of experience. Eager to apply my skills in the real world and with great teams, maintaining, and completing client proposal and ideas. Special interest in achieving growth in and with teams, for the company and career

Professional Experience

SwiftTask Technologies. | Junior Frontend developer 2021 – 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Built and maintain the UI of client's Apps and websites
- Together with team members converts figma and Adobe XD designs into react websites
- Research on ways user interact with interfaces to improve the User experience of client's Apps and websites
- Together with the team, design and manage the Backend of Wesites using django

Daveton Academy | HTML, CSS and JavaScript Coach/mentor

2022 - Now

Key responsibilities:

- Tutor and inspire Aspiring web designers to become familiar and skilled in the frontend stacks
- Design and maintain the Academy Website

My Contact

- oviedavid77@gmail.com
- +234-8149485675
- Warri, Delta State
- https://daveton.vercel.app/

Hard Skill

- HTML5
- CSS 3
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- React.js

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Problem solving
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- University of Benin, Edo State
 Environmental management
 Completed in 2021
- Coursera
 Certification in IT support professional certification
 Ongoing
- Javascript Mastery Master Course
 Certification in Frontend development
 Ongoing

Achievements

2022 – 2023 Built five (5) major projects including my portfolio website, dashboards and online School management Website